{
"jokes": [
 {
   "question": "What do NASA programmers do on the weekends?",
   "answer": "They hit the space bar."
 },
 {
   "question": "I used to work as a programmer for autocorrect....",
   "answer": "Then they fried me for no raisin."
 },
 {
   "question": "If a programmer could rearrange the alphabet, they'd put U and I together.",
   "answer": "User Interface is important to them."
 },
 {
   "question": "What do the programmers do when they pay respect?",
   "answer": "They printf"
 },
 {
   "question": "What does a programmer's ghost say?",
   "answer": "bool!"
 },
 {
   "question": "A programmer's wife tells him: \"While you're at the store, get some milk\".",
   "answer": "He never comes back."
 },
 {
   "question": "Why did the programmer quit his job?",
   "answer": "because he didn't get arrays."
 },
 {
   "question": "Why did the programmer leave his job ?",
   "answer": "Because he couldn’t hack it."
 },
 {
   "question": "What was the SNES programmers' favorite drink?",
   "answer": "Sprite"
 },
 {
   "question": "What do programmers do when they're hungry?",
   "answer": "They grab a byte"
 },
 {
   "question": "Why does programmers have perfect vision?",
   "answer": "Because they can C++"
 },
 {
   "question": "Why couldn't the programmer dance to the song?",
   "answer": "Because he didn't get the... algo-rhythm..."
 },
 {
   "question": "Why do programmers like dark mode?",
   "answer": "Because light attracts bugs"
 },
 {
   "question": "How does the computer programmer order all her books?",
   "answer": "By the Dewey Hexadecimal System!"
 },
 {
   "question": "Children with only a mother make horrible programmers",
   "answer": "Theres always missing paren"
 },
 {
   "question": "How does a programmer get cooler in the summer?",
   "answer": "He opens Windows"
 },
 {
   "question": "As a programmer, waking up is the 0th thing I do every morning",
   "answer": " "
 },
 {
   "question": "What you call it when computer programmers make fun of each other?",
   "answer": "cyber boolean"
 },
 {
   "question": "My friend quit his job as a programmer...",
   "answer": "He didn't get arrays."
 },
 {
   "question": "Programmers hate roman numerals.",
   "answer": "But I can't zero in on why"
 },
 {
   "question": "I am now a succesful programmer",
   "answer": "But back in the days I was a noobgrammer"
 },
 {
   "question": "Why did the programmer get a huge telephone bill?",
   "answer": "Because his program was CALLING a lot of subroutines."
 },
 {
   "question": "What do spanish programmers code in?",
   "answer": "Sí ++"
 },
 {
   "question": "Which way did the programmer go?",
   "answer": "He went data way!"
 },
 {
   "question": "Scientists and programmers have gotten together to write computer code that will not only warn of future global warming but also take credit for inventing the internet.",
   "answer": "It's an new Al-Gore-rithm"
 },
 {
   "question": "What do programmers and exterminators have in common?",
   "answer": "They both spend most of their time fighting bugs."
 },
 {
   "question": "Why did the C++ programmer do so well at his new job as a packaging and design engineer?",
   "answer": "Because he was very good at orienting objects."
 },
 {
   "question": "What do programmers dance to?",
   "answer": "Algorhythms"
 },
 {
   "question": "Why do programmers wear glasses?",
   "answer": "Because they can't C#"
 },
 {
   "question": "Why was the programmer always running into walls?",
   "answer": "He couldn’t see sharp."
 },
 {
   "question": "How programmers curse?",
   "answer": "Oh shift!"
 },
 {
   "question": "People \"without genders\" are usually bad programmers...",
   "answer": "since they're non-binary"
 },
 {
   "question": "Harry Potter was a programmer",
   "answer": "He is fluent in Python"
 },
 {
   "question": "Why do Programmers make good politicians?",
   "answer": "Their goto is to switch statements."
 },
 {
   "question": "How did the Programmer lose weight?",
   "answer": "Hey switched to a byte sized diet."
 },
 {
   "question": "As a computer programmer, I love goose-feather pillows...",
   "answer": "Because they are down-loaded!"
 },
 {
   "question": "Why do programmers only go outside during the winter?",
   "answer": "Because it's code outside."
 },
 {
   "question": "Why was the Asian Dad always disappointed in the programmer kid?",
   "answer": "All he knew was C++."
 },
 {
   "question": "Programmers hate roman numerals.",
   "answer": "But I can't zero in on why?"
 }
]
}